Guide to the Jesse H. Jones Corporate and Property records, 1836-2008 MS 621
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series II: Property Records, 234181
  - Harris County Leagues, 236306
    - Harris and Wilson Two Leagues Grant, 236343
      - Surveys, 239295
        - Harris and Wilson Survey: Miles and Franklin Tracts, 190-1910; 239301 (Box 139, Folder 6)
        - Harris and Wilson Survey: Pasadena (2nd Tier Subdivision), 1912; 239302 (Box 139, Folder 7)
        - Harris and Wilson Survey: Royall Property Abstract, 183201913; 239303 (Box 139, Folder 8)
        - Harris and Wilson Survey: Wilson Property, 1885-1918; 239304 (Box 139, Folder 9)
        - Harris and Wilson Survey: Douglass Tract, 1885-1912; 239305 (Box 139, Folder 10)
    - J.R. Harris League, 239310
      - John R. Harris Survey: Baldwin and Foster Subdivision, 1910-1916; 260080 (Box 139, Folder 11)
      - Baldwin and Foster Subdivison: Outlot 17, 1950; 260082 (Box 139, Folder 12)
      - John R. Harris Survey: Tod and Johnson Subdivision, 1913; 260081 (Box 139, Folder 13)
    - S.M. Harris League, 239311
      - S.M. Harris Survey: Kendall Homestead Abstracts- Houston NSBB, Holley Purchase, 1846-1911; 260083 (Box 139, Folder 14)
      - S.M. Harris Survey: Kendall Homestead Abstracts- NSBB Houston, Holley Purchase, 1907; 260084 (Box 139, Folder 15)
    - Johnson Hunter League, 239307
      - J. Hunter Survey: Block 180, LaPorte, 1896; 260086 (Box 139, Folder 16)
      - J. Hunter Survey: Block 180, LaPorte, 1907-1919; 260085 (Box 139, Folder 17)
      - J. Hunter Survey: Block 180, LaPorte, 1920-1941; 260087 (Box 139, Folder 18)
    - O.P. Kelton 1/3 League, 239306
      - Sarah Francelia Bell Home to Lee P. Brown, 1928-1954; 260088 (Box 139, Folder 19)
    - J. McClosky League, 236353
      - J. McClosky League (I), 1886-1924; 236326 (Box 128, Folder 5)
      - J. McClosky League (II), 1886-1924; 236327 (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - Geo. B. McKinstry League, 239308
      - Various Documents, 1913; 260089 (Box 139, Folder 20)
    - Sarah McKissick League, 239309
      - BMC Loan to: Edith Taylor, 1900-1936; 260090 (Box 139, Folder 21)
      - AA Davis Loan, 1924-1936; 260091 (Box 139, Folder 22)
      - E. Taylor Loan, 1932-1942; 260092 (Box 139, Folder 23)
    - J.W. Moody League/ J.W. Baker League, 260093
      - Ridgeview Farms Co., 1925; 260094 (Box 139, Folder 24)
    - Patrick League, 260095
      - Patrick Survey, 1890; 260104 (Box 139, Folder 25)
    - Various Leagues and Surveys, 260096
      - Various Tax Receipts, 1909-1916; 260105 (Box 139, Folder 26)
      - Various Surveys: 5,287.25 Acres, 1910-1921; 260106 (Box 139, Folder 27)
      - Various Surveys: Wilson Property, 1911-1914; 260107 (Box 139, Folder 28)
    - Wm. Vince League, 260098
      - Various Documents, 1871-1891; 260108 (Box 139, Folder 29)
      - W. Vince Survey: Pasadena- Bolton Farm, 1908; 260109 (Box 139, Folder 30)
    - Robert Wilson League, 260099
      - R. Wilson Survey: Saiboro Property, 1909; 260110 (Box 139, Folder 31)
      - OP Steeger Loan: Webster Subdivision, 1930-1934; 260111 (Box 139, Folder 32)
      - S. Webster Field, 1953-1966; 260112 (Box 139, Folder 33)
      - Webster Farms Co., 1830-1901; 260113 (Box 139, Folder 34)
    - Robert Wilson League/ Sarah Deel League, 260100
      - Webster Farms Co. (1 of 2), 1830-1925; 260114 (Box 139, Folder 35)
      - Webster Farms Co. (2 of 2), 1830-1925; 260115 (Box 139, Folder 36)
      - Various Documents, 1909-1920; 260116 (Box 139, Folder 37)
    - Robert Wilson League/ Sarah Deel League/ John Dickerson League, 260101
      - Webster Farms Co., 1895-1960; 260117 (Box 139, Folder 38)
      - Land Leases, 1931; 260118 (Box 139, Folder 39)
    - Robert Wilson League/ John Dickerson League, 260102
      - Rio Vista Estates, 1959-1960; 260119 (Box 139, Folder 40)
    - Deepwater: Thomas Earle, James Seymour and William Vince Leagues, 260103
      - Deepwater Canal Co: Articles of Incorporation, 1903; 260120 (Box 139, Folder 41)
      - Deepwater Canal Co: Irrigation System, 1906; 260121 (Box 139, Folder 42)
      - Deepwater Canal Co: Irrigation System, 1906; 260122 (Box 139, Folder 43)
      - Deepwater Canal Co: Irrigation System, 1906; 260123 (Box 139, Folder 44)
      - Galveston, Harrisburg, San Antonio RY- W.E. Jones: Canal Maintenance and Operation, 1909; 260124 (Box 139, Folder 45)
      - N.G. Runnels - M. Delehavmes: Thos. Earle Survey, 1868; 260125 (Box 139, Folder 46)
      - Mary Buckley - N.P. Dolen:: Thos. Earle League (Map), 1872; 260127 (Box 139, Folder 47)
      - NP Dolen W.T. Selby: Thos. Earle League, 1872; 260129 (Box 139, Folder 48)
      - Delehaumes - Dolen: Thos. Earle League, 1874; 260130 (Box 139, Folder 49)
      - W.T. Selby - N.P. Dolen: Thos. Earle League, 1875; 260140 (Box 139, Folder 50)
      - J. Darren - N.P. Dolen: Thos. Earle League, 1876; 260144 (Box 139, Folder 51)
      - N.P. Dolen - Hutcheson + Schmidt: Thos. Earle League, 1879; 260146 (Box 139, Folder 52)
      - N.P. Dolen Abstract: Thos. Earle League, c. 1880; 260148 (Box 139, Folder 53)
      - Thomas Earle League Abstract, 1889; 260150 (Box 139, Folder 54)
      - Thomas Earle League Abstract, 1891; 260152 (Box 139, Folder 55)
      - Vick v Unkown Heirsos, Patrick McIntee, et al: Thomas Earle League Abstract, 56; 260160 (Box 139, Folder 56)
      - Vick Heir- W.E. Jones: Thomas Earle League Abstract, 1909; 260162 (Box 139, Folder 57)
      - Thomas Earle Survey: Trackage Agreement, HEI + Navigation Dist., 1928-1969; 260166 (Box 140, Folder 1)
      - Thomas Earle League: Houston Deepwater Land Co., 1929; 260167 (Box 140, Folder 2)
      - Thomas Earle Survey: Various Documents, 1936-1974; 260169 (Box 140, Folder 3)
      - Thomas Earle Survey: Various Documents, 1936-1974; 260170 (Box 140, Folder 4)
      - Thomas Earle Survey: Houston End, Inc., 1943-1975; 260172 (Box 140, Folder 5)
      - Thomas Earle Survey: Grazing Leases, 1958-1977; 260174 (Box 140, Folder 6)
      - Thomas Earle Survey: HEI vs Phillips Pet Co. + Phillips Pipeline Co., 1967-1977; 260176 (Box 140, Folder 7)
      - Thomas Earle Survey: 767,555 Acres Surveyed Appraised, 1969-1974; 260178 (Box 140, Folder 8)
      - Thomas Earle Survey: Easement to Coastal Industrial Water Authority, 1971-1973; 260180 (Box 140, Folder 9)
      - Thomas Earle Survey: Explorer Pipeline Co. Pipeline Crossing, 1970-1971; 260182 (Box 140, Folder 10)
      - Thomas Earle Survey: ETYL Corp Purchase Option, 1971-1972; 260184 (Box 140, Folder 11)
      - Thomas Earle Survey: Exxon Pipeline Co., 1974-1976; 260186 (Box 140, Folder 12)
      - Thomas Earle Survey: Sale to Georgia Pacific Co., 1976-1977; 260187 (Box 140, Folder 14)
      - W.A. + A.E. Evans - W.B. Wilson + O.F. Young- Wm. Vince League- 400 Acres, 1868; 260188 (Box 140, Folder 15)
      - Wilson + Young - Leason, 1871; 260190 (Box 140, Folder 16)
      - Wm. Summer - Wm. Gleason: Wm. Vince League/ James Seymour League, 1872; 260192 (Box 140, Folder 17)
      - Wm. Gleason - N.P. Dolen: Wm. Vince League/ James Seymour League, 1882; 260194 (Box 140, Folder 18)
      - N.P. Dolen - M. Dolen: Wm. Vince League, 1885; 260196 (Box 140, Folder 19)
      - A.J. Vick - J.B. LaGros Et Al: Wm. Vince League, 1894; 260197 (Box 140, Folder 20)
      - Stinard - Vick: Wm. Vince + Jas. Seymour League, 1894; 260199 (Box 140, Folder 21)
      - Dolen-Vick Release: Wm. Vince League + Jas. Seymour League, 1891; 260202 (Box 140, Folder 22)
      - N.P. Dolen-W.D. Ellis: Wm. Vince League + Jas. Seymour League, 1890; 260205 (Box 140, Folder 23)
      - W.D. Ellis - A.J. Vick: Wm. Vince League + Jas. Seymour League, 1891; 260213 (Box 140, Folder 24)
      - A.J. Vick - JH Starkey: Wm. Vince League, Jas. Seymour League, Thos. Earle League, 1894-1898; 260215 (Box 140, Folder 25)
      - Vick vs Mead: Wm. Vince League, Jas. Seymour League, Thos. Earle League, 1894; 260217 (Box 140, Folder 26)
      - A.J. Vick - J.D. Thomas: Jas. Seymour League, Wm. Vince League, 260220 (Box 140, Folder 27)
      - JA Friedman - MT Jones + AJ Vick: Jas. Seymour League, 1895; 260224 (Box 140, Folder 28)
      - JA Friedman - MT Jones + AJ Vick: Jas. Seymour League, 1895; 260229 (Box 140, Folder 29)
      - JH Burnett- MT Jones: Wm. Vince + Jas. Seymour League, 1895; 260230 (Box 140, Folder 30)
      - Am Cate - AJ Vick + MT Jones, 1895; 260231 (Box 140, Folder 31)
      - M. Henry - MT Jones + AJ Vick, 1895; 260233 (Box 140, Folder 32)
      - Title Exam for MT Jones, 1895; 260234 (Box 140, Folder 33)
      - Vick- Barnard Opinion, 1895; 260236 (Box 140, Folder 34)
      - CJ. Brickett- AJ Vick + MT Jones, 1895-1898; 260238 (Box 140, Folder 35)
      - H.W. Culpepper - MT Jones, 1895-1899; 260239 (Box 140, Folder 36)
      - A.J. Vick - M.T. Jones, 1895-1897; 260240 (Box 140, Folder 37)
      - CJ Brockett - AJ Vick, MT Jones, 1895-1898; 260241 (Box 140, Folder 38)
      - Notes Payable, 1895-1906; 260242 (Box 140, Folder 39)
      - Cultivation Contracts, 1896-1897; 260260 (Box 141, Folder 1)
      - H.W. Culpepper- M.T. Jones: Lumber Purchase, 1896; 260262 (Box 141, Folder 2)
      - J.O. Thomas - M.T. Jones, 1896; 260264 (Box 141, Folder 3)
      - M.T. Jones - J. Perry, 1897; 260275 (Box 141, Folder 4)
      - W.F. Lewis - M.T. Jones, 1897; 260276 (Box 141, Folder 5)
      - McQuatters- JH Jones, et al., 1897; 260277 (Box 141, Folder 6)
      - G.F. Seeyla - M.T. Jones Estate: James Seymour and William Vince League, 1897-1898; 260278 (Box 141, Folder 7)
      - M.T. Jones List of Purchases, c. 1898; 260279 (Box 141, Folder 8)
      - J.H. Burnett - M.T. Jones; Wm. Vince + Jas. Seymour Leagues, 1898-1897; 260280 (Box 141, Folder 9)
      - M.T. Jones, H.F. Smith, Deepwater Gin Co: H.F. King, 1898-1899; 260281 (Box 141, Folder 10)
      - J.H. Starkey - W.E. Jones: Rlease of Lien, 1898-1902; 260282 (Box 141, Folder 11)
      - S.D. + H.W. Culpepper - W.E. Jones: Outlot 287, 1900; 260283 (Box 141, Folder 12)
      - Morris Machine Works: Pump, 1902; 260284 (Box 141, Folder 13)
      - J.H. Jones - Rice Crops, 1905; 260285 (Box 141, Folder 14)
      - A.J. Vick - W.E. Jones: James Seymour + Wm. Vince Leagues, 1905; 260286 (Box 141, Folder 15)
      - W.E. Jones - W.F. Jones, 1905-1906; 260287 (Box 141, Folder 16)
      - Miller Bros. + M.E. Com, 1905-1908; 260288 (Box 141, Folder 17)
      - J.E. Ross - W.E. Jones: James Seymour + Wm. Vince Leagues, 1905-1919; 260289 (Box 141, Folder 18)
      - Atlantic Rice Mills Co., 1906; 260290 (Box 141, Folder 19)
      - Rice Threshing + Sales, 1906; 260291 (Box 141, Folder 20)
      - P. Evans - W.E. Jones: Livestock + Equipment Purchase, 1907; 260292 (Box 141, Folder 21)
      - Fish Pond, 1907; 260293 (Box 141, Folder 22)
      - Bullock - Miller Lease, 1907; 260294 (Box 141, Folder 23)
      - Notes, 1907-1911; 260295 (Box 141, Folder 24)
      - Abstract Receipts, 1907-1918; 260296 (Box 141, Folder 25)
      - Casteel - Crossman - Turner - W.E. Jones: Outlots 211-226, 1907-1919; 260297 (Box 141, Folder 26)
      - A. Smith - W.E. Jones: Outlots 109; Townlot 1, Block 17, 1908; 260298 (Box 141, Folder 27)
      - James Seymour + William Vince League: Abstract of Title, Lots 339; 355; 422, 1908; 260299 (Box 141, Folder 28)
      - JH Starkey - W.E. Jones, 1908-1917; 260300 (Box 141, Folder 29)
      - W.E. Jones - E.P. Miller: Agreements and Contracts, 1909-1919; 260301 (Box 141, Folder 30)
      - Insurance Documents, 1909-1927; 260302 (Box 141, Folder 31)
      - W.E. Jones - Mr. Henry, 1910; 260303 (Box 141, Folder 32)
      - San Jacinto Rice Co., 1910; 260304 (Box 141, Folder 33)
      - Edgewood Realty Co. - W.E. Jones, 1911; 260305 (Box 141, Folder 34)
      - Harris + Wilson 2 League Survey, 1912-1929; 260306 (Box 141, Folder 35)
      - Wm. Vince Survey: Outlot 34, 1912-1976; 260307 (Box 141, Folder 36)
      - Jesse H. Jones Lumber Co., 1913; 260308 (Box 141, Folder 37)
      - W.E. Jones Agreements + Settlements, 1913-1918; 260309 (Box 141, Folder 38)
      - W.E. Jones - School District # 40, 1916; 260310 (Box 141, Folder 39)
      - W.E. + Mary Jones - Frank Andrews, 1916-1919; 260311 (Box 141, Folder 40)
      - W.E. Vince Survey: Outlot 34 - Abstracts, 1916-1962; 260312 (Box 141, Folder 41)
      - W.E. Jones - Coons Cypress Silo Co, Inc., 1918; 260317 (Box 141, Folder 42)
      - W.E. Jones - J.W. Sanders: Right-of-Way, 1918; 260319 (Box 141, Folder 43)
      - Deepwater Farm Co: Receipts and Bills, 1918-1919; 260321 (Box 141, Folder 44)
      - M. Tilford Jones - Negotiations, Contracts + Receipts, 1918-1935; 260323 (Box 141, Folder 45)
      - W.E. Jones - E.N. Drouett: Cattle Sale, 260324 (Box 141, Folder 46)
      - M. Tilford Jones - U.S. Railroad Admist., 1919; 260325 (Box 141, Folder 47)
      - L.P. Hammond - W.E. Jones: Earnest Money Contract, 1919; 260326 (Box 141, Folder 48)
      - W.E. Mary B, M.T. Jones - P.C. Thompson, 1919; 260327 (Box 141, Folder 50)
      - W.E. Jones - Mary B. Jones, 1919; 260330 (Box 141, Folder 51)
      - I.P. Poyner vs. W.E. Jones, 1919; 260331 (Box 141, Folder 52)
      - P.C. Thompson - W.E. Jones: Commission Agreement, 1919-1920; 260332 (Box 141, Folder 53)
      - M. Tilford Jones to Houston Terminal Land Co., 1919-1928; 260333 (Box 141, Folder 54)
      - W.E. Jones: Land Owned in Fee, 1920; 260334 (Box 141, Folder 55)
      - M. Tilford Jones: Financial Records, 1921-1930; 260335 (Box 141, Folder 56)
      - M. Tilford + W.E. Jones - Port Houston Realty Co., 1924-1929; 260337 (Box 141, Folder 57)
      - W.E. + M. Tilford Jones: Financial Records, 1924-1930; 260338 (Box 141, Folder 58)
      - M. Tilford Jones, A.T. Vick, P.T. Houston Relaty Co: Wm. Vince League Block 18, 1924-1931; 260339 (Box 141, Folder 59)
      - Albert J. Buford - M. Tilford Jones: Wm. Vince League, 19124-1934; 260340 (Box 141, Folder 60)
      - James Seymour + William Vince League Absteact of Title, MT. Jones, 1924; 260341 (Box 141, Folder 61)
      - James Spencer + William Vince League: Abstract of Title, MT Jones, 1924; 260342 (Box 141, Folder 62)
      - James Seymour + William Vince League: Abstract of Title, 1924-1938; 260343 (Box 141, Folder 63)
      - Grazing Leases, 1929-1951; 260344 (Box 141, Folder 64)
      - Harris County - M. Tilford Jones: Quit Cliam Deed Channel City Road, 1931; 260345 (Box 141, Folder 65)
      - Houston Deepwater Land Co. - M. Tilford Jones - J.H. Jones, 1930; 260346 (Box 141, Folder 66)
      - M. Tilford Jones - Title Dispute, 1930; 260347 (Box 141, Folder 67)
      - J.H. Jones + Co: Finanicial Records, 1930; 260348 (Box 141, Folder 68)
      - Houston Deepwater Land Co: Financial Records, 1930-1935; 260349 (Box 141, Folder 69)
      - Wm. Vince Survey: Out Lot 34, 1933-1966; 260350 (Box 141, Folder 70)
      - Houston Deepwater Land Co. - KTRH Broadcast Co; M. Tilford Jones, 1935-1948; 260355 (Box 142, Folder 1)
      - J.H. Jones, 1933; 260357 (Box 142, Folder 2)
      - Baker, Botts, Andrews + Wharton: Opinions, 1937; 260359 (Box 142, Folder 3)
      - F.J. Heyne Affadavit, 1937; 260360 (Box 142, Folder 4)
      - Houston Deepwater Land Co. + Mason Investment Co. - USA, 1937; 260361 (Box 142, Folder 5)
      - Houston Deepwater Land Co. - U.S. of America, 1914-1942; 260362 (Box 142, Folder 6)
      - KTRH Broadcasting Co. - Harris City Broadcasting Co: James Seymour + Thomas Earle Survey, 1948; 260363 (Box 142, Folder 7)
      - Beck Cattle + Land Co., 1948-1952; 260364 (Box 142, Folder 8)
      - Beck Cattle + Land Co., 1948-1956; 260365 (Box 142, Folder 9)
      - Beck Cattle + Land Co. - Houston Deepwater Land Co, 1949; 260366 (Box 142, Folder 10)
      - Beck Cattle + Land Co., 1952-1956; 260367 (Box 142, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, 1953-1955; 260368 (Box 142, Folder 12)
      - Wm. Vince Survey: Outlot 34, 1962-1969; 260369 (Box 142, Folder 13)
      - Wm. Vince Survey: Outlot 34, 1963-1975; 260371 (Box 142, Folder 14)
      - Wm. Vince Survey: Outlot 34, Sale to Nelson Services, 1964-1977; 260372 (Box 142, Folder 15)
      - Wm. Vince Survey: Outlot 34, Sale to Atl. Richfield, 1974-1977; 260374 (Box 142, Folder 16)
      - Wm. Vince Survey: Outlot 34, Sale to Darby + Asso., 1972-1976; 260375 (Box 142, Folder 17)
      - Various Surveys - Easements + Leases, 1920-1950; 260378 (Box 142, Folder 18)
      - Various Surveys - Leases, 1925-1959; 260380 (Box 142, Folder 19)
      - Pipeline Proposal, n.d.; 260382 (Box 142, Folder 20)
  - Harris County Surveys, 260410
    - John Austin Survey/ Obediance Smith Survey, 260384
      - Susholtz Loan, 1928-1945; 260383 (Box 142, Folder 21)
    - HS Bachelder Survey/ James Baily Survey, 260387
      - BMC Loan to: Cambridge Corp., 1957-1961; 260422 (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - James Baily Survey, 260388
      - BMC Loan to: Cambridge Mort Co. Keswick Place Sub-Divison, Various Blocks + Lots, 1959-1960; 260424 (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - J.S. Black Survey/ C.V. Uglow Survey, 260411
      - Various Documents, 1913; 260426 (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - Boatright Survey, 260412
      - Landleases, 1935; 260427 (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - Nicholas Brady Survey, 260413
      - J.H. Seiber Purchase; Forest Acres Sub-Division, 1927-1944; 260428 (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - John Brown Survey, 260414
      - Tide Water Sub-Division: Scott Armstrong Pruchase By the Farifax Corp., 1901-1947; 260430 (Box 143, Folder 6)
      - Houston Ship Channel, 1938-1956; 260432 (Box 143, Folder 7)
      - Houston Ship Channel, 1938-1956; 260433 (Box 143, Folder 8)
      - Houston Ship Channel, 1951; 260434 (Box 143, Folder 9)
    - J.M. Dement Survey, 260415
      - Davant, Eversberg, + Jacobs Land, 1932-1936; 260435 (Box 143, Folder 10)
      - 1/3 League Survey: Land Lease, 1933; 260436 (Box 143, Folder 11)
      - Fairbanks Field, 1938-1982; 260437 (Box 143, Folder 12)
    - John Gay Survey, 260416
      - W.S. McDowell Sale, 1956; 260438 (Box 143, Folder 13)
    - H+T.C.R.R. Co. Survey, 260417
      - BMC Loan: J.W. Hilmer, Little York Subdivision, 1931-1937; 260439 (Box 143, Folder 14)
      - Block 2 Sect. 22 + 28: Halsey + Caldwell Loan, 1938-1943; 260440 (Box 143, Folder 15)
    - H.T. + B.R.R. Co. Survey #12, 260442
      - Land Lease, 1934-1937; 260443 (Box 143, Folder 16)
    - F. Hamilton Survey, 260418
      - F. Hamilton Survey, 1892-1894; 260444 (Box 143, Folder 17)
    - James Hamilton Survey, 260419
      - S. Minchen Sale, 1918-1951; 260445 (Box 143, Folder 18)
    - Holman Survey #4, 260420
      - Block C Lots, 1906; 260446 (Box 143, Folder 19)
      - Block C Tax Receipts, 1906-1911; 260447 (Box 143, Folder 20)
      - Block C Lots 1-16, 1908; 260448 (Box 143, Folder 21)
      - Block C Lots 3-7, 9-10, 15, 1909-1910; 260451 (Box 143, Folder 22)
      - Block C Lots 9, 1911-1917; 260452 (Box 143, Folder 23)
      - Block 4 Lot 10, 1913; 260453 (Box 143, Folder 24)
    - Holman Survey #5, 260421
      - Block ?, Lot 12, 1913-1914; 260454 (Box 143, Folder 25)
      - Block 1, Lot 12-15, 1906-1909; 260455 (Box 143, Folder 26)
      - Block 1, Lot 8-11,15-16, 1906-1910; 260456 (Box 143, Folder 27)
      - Block 1, Tax Receipts, 1906-1911; 260457 (Box 143, Folder 28)
      - Block 1, Lots 1-2, 1906-1912; 260458 (Box 143, Folder 29)
      - Block 1, Lots 8-9, 1906-1913; 260459 (Box 143, Folder 30)
      - Block 1, Lots 1-2, 10-16, 1908; 260460 (Box 143, Folder 31)
      - Block 1, Lots 3-4, 1909-1922; 260461 (Box 143, Folder 32)
      - Block 1, Lots 13, 1910; 260462 (Box 143, Folder 33)
      - Block 1, Lots 11, 1915; 260463 (Box 143, Folder 34)
      - Block 1, Lots 4, 15-16: MRS, E.T. Scruggs Loan, 1922-1923; 260464 (Box 143, Folder 35)
      - Block 2, Tax Receipts, 1906-1911; 260465 (Box 143, Folder 36)
      - Block 2, Lots 1-16, 1906-1914; 260466 (Box 143, Folder 37)
      - Block 2, Lots 9, 1911; 260467 (Box 143, Folder 38)
      - Block 2, Lots 15, 1911; 260468 (Box 143, Folder 39)
      - Block 2, Lots 16, 1911-1914; 260469 (Box 143, Folder 40)
      - Block 2, Lots 4-5, 1911-1915; 260470 (Box 143, Folder 41)
      - Block 2, Lots 1-3, 6-7, 12-14, 1911-1916; 260471 (Box 143, Folder 42)
      - Block 2, Lots 10-11, 1912; 260472 (Box 143, Folder 43)
      - Block 2, Lots 8, 1914; 260473 (Box 143, Folder 44)
      - Block 2, Lots 3: Alex Silverstein Loan, 1921; 260474 (Box 143, Folder 45)
      - Block 3, All Lots, 1905-1916; 260475 (Box 143, Folder 46)
      - Block 3, Tax Receipts, 1906-1911; 260476 (Box 143, Folder 47)
      - Block 3, Lots 1-3, 5-6, 1911; 260477 (Box 143, Folder 48)
      - Block 3, Lot 15, 1911-1914; 260478 (Box 143, Folder 49)
      - Block 3, Lot 16, 1912; 260479 (Box 143, Folder 50)
      - Block 3, Lots 10, 16, 1915; 260480 (Box 143, Folder 51)
      - Block 3, Lots 11-13, 1918; 260481 (Box 143, Folder 52)
      - Block 4, All Lots, 1905-1910; 260482 (Box 143, Folder 53)
      - Block 4, Tax Receipts, 1906-1911; 260483 (Box 143, Folder 54)
      - Block 4 Lots H2, 1907-1921; 260488 (Box 144, Folder 1)
      - Block 4 Lots 3-16, 1908; 260489 (Box 144, Folder 2)
      - Block 4 Lots 8-10, 1910; 260491 (Box 144, Folder 3)
      - Block 4 Lots 13, 1910-1915; 260492 (Box 144, Folder 4)
      - Block 4 Lots 15, 1910-1915; 260494 (Box 144, Folder 5)
      - Block 4 Lots 4, 1911; 260495 (Box 144, Folder 6)
      - Block 4 Lots 13, 1912; 260496 (Box 144, Folder 7)
      - Block 4 Lots 14, 1915; 260498 (Box 144, Folder 8)
      - Block 4 Lots 14: 2501 Chartres Wood Loan, 1918-1923; 260499 (Box 144, Folder 9)
      - Block 4 Lots 5-6; 15, 1920-1921; 260500 (Box 144, Folder 10)
    - Holman Survey #6, 260502
      - Block 3 Lots 6-7, 1916; 260501 (Box 144, Folder 11)
    - Holman Survey #7, 260503
      - Block 1 Lots 1-4, 1910-1916; 260507 (Box 144, Folder 12)
      - Block 1 Lots 1-2: Frank Russell- Trustee for W.A. Smith, 1921; 260508 (Box 144, Folder 13)
    - Holman Survey #8, 260504
      - Block C Lots 4-8, 1906-1913; 260510 (Box 144, Folder 14)
    - Holman Survey #9, 260505
      - Block 4 Lots 5-10, 1900-1919; 260511 (Box 144, Folder 15)
      - Hutcheson's Addition Block 4 Abstracts of Title, 1909; 1917; 260513 (Box 144, Folder 16)
      - Wespar Realty Co. Property- Abstracts of Title, 1919; 260514 (Box 144, Folder 17)
      - Wespar Realty Co. Property- Abstracts of Title, Block 4, 1920-1928; 260515 (Box 144, Folder 18)
      - Leases- Block 4 Lots 6,7,8,9 +10, Main and Bernard, 1938-1942; 260516 (Box 144, Folder 19)
      - BMC Purchase From Gulf Oil Co. Blocks 4 Lots 5+6, 1949-1962; 260517 (Box 144, Folder 20)
      - Wespar Realty Co. Property Block 4 Lots 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 1926-1962; 260518 (Box 144, Folder 21)
      - Abstract of Title- Lot 5; 5.35 ft. Lot 6, Block 4, 1952; 260519 (Box 144, Folder 22)
      - Block 4 Lots 6-10 Texas Motor Exchange, 2406-10 Main St., 1959-1971; 260520 (Box 144, Folder 23)
      - Block 4 Lots 5-10 Mossy Oldsmobile (Menger) 2400 Main, 1972-1986; 260521 (Box 144, Folder 24)
    - Holman Survey #10, 260506
      - Tract 2 Lots 6+7, 1908-1924; 260522 (Box 144, Folder 25)
      - Various Documents, 1910-1924; 260523 (Box 144, Folder 26)
      - Tract 2 Lots 6+7 Construction Center, Gydeson-Manferd Cadillac, 2400 Main, 1919; 260524 (Box 144, Folder 27)
      - Tract 2 Lots 6+7, Leases, 1923-1933; 260525 (Box 144, Folder 28)
      - Tract 2 Lots 6+7, Insurance 2400 Main, 1925-1932; 260526 (Box 144, Folder 29)
      - Tract 2 Lots 6+7, 2404-08 Main Trust Motors, 1928-1932; 260527 (Box 144, Folder 30)
      - Tract 2 Lots 6+7, 2404-10 Main Leases, Evans Motor Co., 1934; 260528 (Box 144, Folder 31)
      - Tract 2 Lots 6+7, Jackson Motors, 1934-1936; 260529 (Box 144, Folder 32)
      - Holman Survey + Obedience Smith Survey: 3 Tracts of Land (I), 1839-1951; 260530 (Box 144, Folder 33)
      - Holman Survey + Obedience Smith Survey: 3 Tracts of Land (II), 1839-1951; 260531 (Box 144, Folder 34)
      - The Northfield Co. (Main St.), 1908-1968; 260532 (Box 144, Folder 35)
      - H+D Corp. (Main St.), 1951-1974; 260533 (Box 144, Folder 36)